https://www.ccrcanada.com/terms-of-use/

Terms Of Use
www.ccrcanada.com
This version in effect since June 29th, 2012
ATTENTION: PLEASE READ THESE TERMS CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE. USING THIS WEBSITE INDICATES THAT YOU ACCEPT THESE TERMS. IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT THESE TERMS (“TERMS”), DO NOT USE THIS WEBSITE.
WELCOME TO CCR CLEANROOM PRODUCTS (“CCR”).  PLEASE READ THIS AGREEMENT CAREFULLY AS IT GOVERNS YOUR USE OF THE CCRCANADA.COM WEBSITE. IT EXEMPTS CCR AND OTHER PERSONS FROM LIABILITY OR LIMITS THEIR LIABILITY, AND CONTAINS OTHER IMPORTANT PROVISIONS THAT YOU SHOULD READ.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS AGREEMENT
This is an Agreement between you and all persons you represent (and for purposes of this Agreement, “person” includes natural persons and any type of incorporated or unincorporated entity) and CCR regarding your access to and use of the www.ccrcanada.com website and all content, information, products and services available on or through the website (collectively, this “website”). This Agreement also provides benefits to CCR affiliates, service providers, suppliers, and other persons.
Each time you use this website you signify your acceptance and agreement, and the acceptance and agreement of any person you purport to represent, to be bound by this Agreement as it then reads, and you represent and warrant that you have the legal authority to agree to and accept this Agreement on behalf of yourself and any person you purport to represent. If you do not agree with each provision of this Agreement, or you are not authorized to agree to and accept this Agreement on behalf of the person you purport to represent, you may not access or use this website. This Agreement is in addition to any other agreement you may have with CCR, including a transaction agreement.
OWNERSHIP AND PERMITTED USE OF THE WEBSITE
This website (including all content, page headers, custom graphics, button icons, scripts and the presentation, arrangement, coordination, enhancement and selection of such and other information in text, graphical, forms, images, icons, designs, applications, data, and other elements available on or through this website) is the property of CCR or its vendors, and is protected by Canadian and international copyright, trademark and other laws. Your use of this website does not transfer to you any ownership or other rights in this website or its content. This website is made available to you for your lawful, personal use only. You may use this website only in the manner described expressly in this Agreement and subject to all applicable laws. Using this website for any other purpose or in any other manner is strictly prohibited.
You may print website pages provided that you do not modify any of the pages and you do not remove or alter any visible or non-visible identification, marks, notices, or disclaimers. This website and its contents may not be copied, imitated, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, modified, indexed, catalogued, mirrored or distributed in any way, in whole or in part, without the express prior written consent of CCR. You may not sell or resell any part of this website or access to the website. You may not use any of the charts that are used in the operation or provision of this website except while you are using the website in accordance with this Agreement.
MISPRINTS AND ERRORS, PRODUCT AVAILABILITY AND PRICES
CCR endeavors to provide current and accurate information on this website. However, misprints, errors, inaccuracies, omissions (including incorrect specifications, descriptions, item numbers or compatibility charts for products) or other errors may sometimes occur. CCR cannot guarantee that products and services advertised on this website will be available when ordered or thereafter. CCR does not warrant that the content of this website including, without limitation, product descriptions or photographs, is accurate or complete.
CCR reserves the right to: (a) correct any error, inaccuracy or omission at any time without prior notice or liability to you or any other person; (b) change at any time the products and services advertised. The advertisements on this website are invitations to you to make offers to purchase products and services on the website and are not offers to sell.
TRADE-MARK INFORMATION
CCR, 3M, Ansell, Texwipe, Veltek, Whileline and other names and logos appearing on or in connection with this website (the “Marks”) are registered or unregistered trademarks, service marks, trade names and logos owned or licensed by CCR or their respective owners or licensees. Any use of the Marks, except as expressly provided in this Agreement, is strictly prohibited. Nothing appearing on this website or elsewhere shall be construed as granting, by implication, estoppel, or otherwise, any licence or right to use any of the Marks.
NO LINKING, FRAMING, MIRRORING, SCRAPING OR DATA-MINING
Links to this website without the express written permission of CCR is strictly prohibited. To request permission to link to this website, please send an email to info@ccrcanada.com. CCR may in its discretion cancel and revoke any permission it may give to link to this website at any time and without any notice or liability. The framing, mirroring, scraping or data-mining of this website or any of the contents in any form and by any means is strictly prohibited. You may not use any collaborative browsing or display technologies in connection with your use of the website or to post comments, communications, or any other data of any kind to or on the website with the intention that such postings may be viewed by other users of the website.
UNSOLICITED SUBMISSIONS
In order to avoid potential misunderstandings or disputes, CCR does not accept or consider unsolicited ideas or suggestions (“Submissions”). If you send Submissions to CCR or the website, you automatically grant (or warrant that the owner of the Submissions grants) to CCR and its successors, assigns and licensees a perpetual, royalty-free, irrevocable, unrestricted, non-exclusive, world-wide, assignable, sub-licensable, right and license to use and exploit the Submissions or any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques associated with the Submissions for any purpose whatsoever, commercial or otherwise, using any form, media or technology now known or later developed, without providing any attribution or compensation to you or any other person, without any liability whatsoever, and free from any obligation of confidence or other duties on the part of CCR or its successors, assigns and licensees, and you agree, represent and warrant that all moral rights in the Submissions are waived in favour of CCR and its successors, assigns and licensees.
YOUR INFORMATION
All information you provide through this website including name, email and messages, must be true, accurate, current and complete. CCR will rely on the information you provide. You will be solely responsible and liable for any and all loss, damage, and additional costs that you, CCR or any other person may incur as a result of your submission of any false, incorrect or incomplete information
PERSONAL INFORMATION PRIVACY
CCR collects, uses and discloses personal information in accordance with its Privacy Policy. The Privacy Policy is available on this website and may be changed from time to time by CCR in its discretion without any notice or liability to you or any other person by making an amended Privacy Policy accessible through this website. By accepting this Agreement, and each time you visit and/or use the website, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information by CCR in accordance with the Privacy Policy as it then reads.
DISCLAIMERS, LIABILITY EXCLUSIONS/LIMITATIONS AND INDEMNITY
DISCLAIMERS
YOUR ACCESS TO AND USE OF THE WEBSITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. THE WEBSITE IS PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS, WITHOUT ANY REPRESENTATIONS, WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AND INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION IMPLIED REPRESENTATIONS, WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF OR RELATING TO ACCURACY, ACCESSIBILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, MERCHANTABILITY, PERFORMANCE OR DURABILITY, ALL OF WHICH ARE DISCLAIMED BY CCR TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.
LIABILITY EXCLUSIONS
CCR AND ITS PROVIDERS WILL NEVER BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY OTHER PERSON FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE OR EXEMPLARY LOSS OR DAMAGE ARISING FROM, CONNECTED WITH, OR RELATING TO THE WEBSITE OR THIS AGREEMENT INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO LOSS OF DATA, BUSINESS, MARKETS, SAVINGS, INCOME, PROFITS, USE, PRODUCTION, REPUTATION OR GOODWILL, ANTICIPATED OR OTHERWISE, OR ECONOMIC LOSS, UNDER ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY (WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY OR ANY OTHER THEORY OR LAW OR EQUITY), REGARDLESS OF ANY NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER FAULT OR WRONGDOING (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION GROSS NEGLIGENCE AND FUNDAMENTAL BREACH) BY CCR OR ANY PERSON FOR WHOM CCR IS RESPONSIBLE, AND EVEN IF CCR HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS OR DAMAGE BEING INCURRED
ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND EXCLUSION BY STATUTE IN CERTAIN JURISDICTIONS
THE EXCLUSION OF CERTAIN WARRANTIES AND THE LIMITATION OF CERTAIN LIABILITIES IS PROHIBITED IN SOME JURISDICTIONS. THESE STATUTORY PROHIBITIONS MAY APPLY TO YOU.
OTHER WEBSITES/RESOURCES
For your convenience, this website may include links or references to other Internet sites or resources and businesses operated by other persons (collectively “Other Sites”). Other Sites are independent from CCR, and CCR has no responsibility or liability for or control over Other Sites, their business, goods, services, or content. CCR does not sponsor or endorse Other Sites or their business, goods, services, or content, unless expressly indicated in writing. Your use of Other Sites and your dealings with the owners or operators of Other Sites is at your own risk, and you will not make any claim against CCR arising from, connected with, or relating to your use of Other Sites or your dealings with the owners or operators of Other Sites. As between you and CCR, this Agreement, with all necessary modifications, applies to your access and use of any Other Sites and their business, goods, services and content.
TERMINATION
Notwithstanding any other provision of this Agreement,CCR may in its discretion change, discontinue, modify, restrict, suspend or terminate this website or any part of it without any notice or liability to you or any other person. CCR may in its discretion and convenience at any time immediately terminate, temporarily or permanently, this Agreement or your permission to access and use the website without any notice or liability to you or any other person.
If this Agreement or your permission to access or use all or any part of the website is terminated for any reason, then this Agreement and all other then existing agreements between you and CCR will continue to apply and be binding upon you regarding your prior access to and use of this website, and anything connected with, relating to or arising there from.
GOVERNING LAW AND DISPUTE RESOLUTION
This Agreement, your access to and use of this website, and all related matters are governed solely by the laws of Ontario and applicable federal laws of Canada. Any dispute between you and CCR  or any other person arising from, connected with or relating to this website, this Agreement, or any related matters (collectively “Disputes”) will be resolved before the Courts of Ontario, sitting in the city of Ottawa, and you hereby irrevocably submit and attorn to the original and exclusive jurisdiction of those courts in respect of all Disputes.
Without limiting the foregoing, you irrevocably and unconditionally: (a) agree that any suit, action, or other legal proceeding arising out of your use of this website including any transaction conducted on or through this website must be brought in a court of record of Ontario in the city of Ottawa (b) consent to the jurisdiction of the courts of Ontario in any such suit, action, or proceeding; (c) waive any objection which you may have to the laying of the venue of any such suit, action or proceeding in any of such courts; and (d) waive any right that you may have to assert the defence of forum non-convenience in any such suit, action or proceeding. CCR makes no representation that materials or services at this website are appropriate or available for use outside of Canada, and access to them from territories where their contents are illegal is prohibited. You may not use or export or re-export the materials or services at this website or any copy or adaptation in violation of any applicable laws or regulations. If you choose to access this website from outside of Canada, you do so at your own initiative and are responsible for compliance with any local laws may be eventually applicable.
OTHER MATTER
If any provision of this Agreement is held to be invalid or unenforceable for any reason, then the provision will be deemed to be severed from this Agreement and the remaining provisions will continue in full force and effect. This Agreement ensures to the benefit of and is binding upon each of CCR and its successors, assigns and related persons, and you and your heirs, executors, administrators, successors, permitted assigns and personal representatives. You may not assign this Agreement or the rights and obligations under this Agreement. CCR may assign this Agreement and its rights and obligations under this Agreement without your consent. No consent or waiver by any party to or of any breach or default by any other party in its performance of its obligations under this Agreement will be: (a) deemed or construed to be a consent to or waiver of a continuing breach or default or any other breach or default of those or any other obligations of that party; or (b) effective unless in writing and signed by all parties.
The parties have expressly requested and required that this Agreement and all other related documents be drawn up in the English language.
CHANGES TO THIS AGREEMENT
CCR may, in its sole discretion, change this Agreement from time to time as it relates to future use of this website, by posting a revised Agreement on the website. By using this website after this revised Agreement has been posted, you signify your acceptance and agreement to be bound by the revised Agreement. You may not change this Agreement in any manner.
Any rights not expressly granted by this Agreement are reserved to CCR.
You may contact CCR by email or postal mail at:
CCR. All Rights Reserved.
Terms Of Use
Privacy Policy
